Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Additions
  - New York State Concerns, 1977-1981 (Folder 70.5)
  - New York State — Long Range Planning, 1979-1980 (Folder 70.6)
  - New York State Heds Hegis, 1980 (Folder 70.7)
  - New York State Education Department — Heds/Hegis Data Collection, 1980 (Folder 70.8)
  - New York State Education Department — Heds/Hegis Data Collection, 1979 (Folder 70.9)
  - New York State Mortgage Agency, 1982-1983 (Folder 70.10)
  - Office Relocation (Including Floor Plans), 1979-1980 (Folder 70.11)
  - Interview — Raymond Parker, Apr 1985 (Folder 70.12)
  - Parents’ Weekend, 1982 (Folder 70.13)
  - Pattern for Progress, 1983 (Folder 70.14)
  - Pattern for Progress — Mid-Hudson, 1979-1982 (Folder 70.15)
  - Mid-Hudson “Pattern for Progress”, 1981-1983 (Folder 70.16)
  - Auditor’s Report — Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co., Jun 1980 (Folder 70.17)
  - Personnel Vouchers, 1978-1980 (Folder 70.18)
  - Philadelphia Show House Preview Party, Apr 1985 (Folder 70.19)
  - Pink Sheets, 1983-1984 (Folder 70.20)
  - Porter Gift, 1981 (Folder 70.21)
  - Poughkeepsie Area Chamber of Commerce, 1982 (Folder 70.22)
  - President’s Advisory Group (Follow-Up), 1982-1983 (Folder 70.23)
  - President’s Advisory Group, 1981-1982 (Folder 70.24)
  - President’s Advisory Group, 1980-1981 (Folder 70.25)
  - President’s Advisory Group, 1979-1981 (Folder 70.26)
  - President’s Entertainment, 1978-1980 (Folder 70.27)
  - Pulver, Patricia (Confidential), 1980 (Folder 70.28)
  - Project 1984 Symposium, Mar 1984 (Folder 70.29)
  - Questionnaires, 1979-1981 (Folder 70.30)
  - Requests for Pamphlets, Information, Etc., 1983-1985 (Folder 70.31)
  - Requests — Letters of Reference/Nominations, 1983-1985 (Folder 70.32)
  - Requests for Pamphlets, Information, Etc., 1979-1984 (Folder 70.33)
  - Resorts for Conferences, 1980-1982 (Folder 70.34)
  - Retrenchment, 1982 (Folder 70.35)
  - Ritterskamp Party, Mar 1981 (Folder 70.36)
  - Joan Robinson, Oct 1982 (Folder 70.37)
  - Rockefeller Dinner, Apr 1981 (Folder 70.38)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Trip to Italy, 1980 (Folder 70.39)
  - S — General, 1981-1983 (Folder 70.40)
  - S — General, 1979-1980 (Folder 70.41)
  - SOS, 1983-1985 (Folder 70.42)
  - Swarthmore College — Advisory Committee on Resource Use, Apr 1979 (Folder 70.43)
  - S.A.C Proposals, 1979 (Folder 70.44)
  - Salute to Women in Industry, Apr 1985 (Folder 70.45)
  - Russell-Sage, 1971-1983 (Folder 70.46)
  - Salaries — Confidential, 1979-1981 (Folder 70.47)
  - Salzburg Alumni Newsletter, 1982 (Folder 70.48)
  - Secretarial Wage Survey, 1980 (Folder 70.49)
  - Sexual Harrassment (Confidential), 1981-1983 (Folder 70.50)
  - Sexual Harrassment (Follow-Up) (Confidential), 1982-1983 (Folder 70.51)
  - Senior Receptions President’s House, 1978-1980 (Folder 70.52)
  - Sexual Harrassment, 1979 (Folder 70.53)
  - Shakespeare Garden, 1980-1981 (Folder 70.54)
  - Mina Pendo Shaughnessy — Memorial Conference, Apr 1980 (Folder 71.1)
  - Shaughnessy Draft, 1980 (Folder 71.2)
  - Dixie Sheridan’s Speeches (Folder 71.3)
  - Alan Simpson, 1977-1984 (Folder 71.4)
  - Sloan Foundation — Meeting of Presidents, Oct 1984 (Folder 71.5)
  - Society for Research into Higher Education, 1982 (Folder 71.6)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, 1978-1980 (Folder 71.7)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, 1978-1979 (Folder 71.8)
  - SOS — August Workshop, 1982 (Folder 71.9)
  - South Africa, 1978 (Folder 71.10)
  - President’s Staff Meeting, 1982-1983 (Folder 71.11)
  - President’s Reception, 1979-1980 (Folder 71.12)
  - Responses to President’s Reception, Sep 1978 (Folder 71.13)
  - Staff Association of Vassar, 1977-1984 (Folder 71.14)
  - Statue of Liberty/Ellis Island, 1983-1984 (Folder 71.15)
  - Steno Bureau Mailing Lists, 1980 (Folder 71.16)
  - D. Stoller — Supt. of Grounds, 1982 (Folder 71.17)
  - Meryl Streep, 1983-1985 (Folder 71.18)
  - Strong, John (Roof Incident), 1985 (Folder 71.19)
  - Dr. Mary Stuart Interview, 1980 (Folder 71.20)
  - Development, 1983-1984 (Folder 71.21)
  - Herbert L. Shultz — Special Assistant, 1980-1983 (Folder 71.22)
  - Personnel Office, 1976-1981 (Folder 71.23)
  - President — Personal, 1979-1986 (Folder 71.24)
  - VBS File (loose materials), 1977-1997 (Folder 71.25)
  - Unprocessed additions, circa 1970-1979 (Box 72)
  - Unprocessed additions, 1999, 2010 (Box 73)